{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Test",
      "description": "Deck",
      "id": 72
    },
    {
      "name": "Ugh",
      "description": "test",
      "id": 40
    },
    {
      "name": "XXX",
      "description": "X",
      "id": 27
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "front",
      "back": "back",
      "deckId": 72,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "front",
      "back": "back",
      "deckId": 40,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "front 1",
      "back": "back 1",
      "deckId": 40,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "front 2",
      "back": "back 2",
      "deckId": 40,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "front 3",
      "back": "back 3",
      "deckId": 40,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "please help",
      "back": "i am lost",
      "deckId": 27,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "x",
      "back": "x",
      "deckId": 27,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "e",
      "back": "e",
      "deckId": 27,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "sdaf",
      "back": "sdf",
      "deckId": 27,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "idk",
      "back": "i am hopeless",
      "deckId": 27,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "asdf",
      "back": "fffffffffffffff",
      "deckId": 27,
      "id": 17
    }
  ]
}